[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
(This drama is a work of fiction)
(Any similarity to real people,
organizations, or events is coincidental)
[faint dog barking]
[cheerful music]
(Dareum) He seems completely unfazed.
[whoosh sound]
[Dareum gasps]
[pants]
That was like a car accident.
(Hagi) I mean...
It was a minor accident.
[laughs]
Right. A minor accident.
(Dareum) Right.
I was just trying to catch this.
The wind suddenly blew it away...
[laughs awkwardly]
Yeah.
Why did this have to fly away like that?
[exhales]
[whoosh sound]
(Dareum) Unlike me,
I'm sure he's dated people before.
[music stops]
(Hagi) I...
Get home safely, then.
You too, Mr. Kang.
Thank you for today.
(Hagi) Bye, then.
[footsteps fading]
(Dareum) Am I the only one
affected by that?
[spraying]
[lid clicks]
(Hagi) That was like a car accident.
[cheerful music]
[heart beating sound]
I mean...
It was a minor accident.
A minor accident.
[whoosh sound]
[music stops]
That...
was my first kiss...
[taps]
Jeez.
[cheerful music continues]
How is he so unfazed?
Is he a player or what?
[sighs]
[heart beating sound]
[grunts]
(Dareum) But why
is my heart beating so fast?
[heartbeat sound continues]
[sighs]
[music stops]
[phone vibrating]
[gasps]
[message notification sound]
(Lee Chan) Dareum,
did you get home safely?
[phone clacks]
[sighs]
[exhales]
What's wrong with me?
[street sounds]
[door opens]
(Episode 7)
- (Yeongwoo) A friend...
- (Mina) Oh...
[Dareum yawns]
[Mina laughs]
Did you not get enough sleep last night?
- (Yeongwoo) You look a bit tired.
- (Mina) Yeah.
[Dareum laughs]
Well...
I couldn't sleep a wink.
(Mina) Why couldn't you sleep a wink?
(Yeongwoo) There are days like that.
[Mina reacts]
[yawns]
[elevator dings]
[sniffles]
[Dareum grunts]
[Mina reacts]
(Yeongwoo) Hello.
I'll go to the corner...
[employees greeting each other]
(Dareum, Mina) Excuse me.
- (automated voice) Doors closing.
- (Dareum) Sorry.
[elevator doors close]
[Dareum gasps]
[intriguing music]
[Dareum grunts]
[thud sound]
[employees gasp]
I'm sorry...
[thud sound]
[employees gasp]
(Yeongwoo) What is it?
- (Dareum) Sorry...
- (Mina) Oh, gosh.
[music stops]
I'll move to this side...
[upbeat music]
- (Hagi) Excuse me.
- (Dareum) Sorry.
(Hagi) Just a moment.
[comical sound]
[Mina grunts]
(Mina) Mr. Kang!
There's someone right here, sir.
[comical sound]
Mr. Kang, I'm standing right here.
It's me, Mina. Lee Mina!
[ding sound]
[Mina grunts]
[Dareum sighs]
(Dareum) Am I...
the only one who feels embarrassed?
[music stops]
(Mina) Can he not see me?
[squeaking sound]
[cat meowing sound]
[intriguing music]
[comical sound]
[cat meowing sound]
[music stops]
(Chandong) Mr. Lee.
Thank you for deciding so quickly.
(Lee Chan) Not at all.
I could hardly sleep
after receiving the offer yesterday.
It's been a long-time dream of mine
to work with you, Director.
[Wonbin, PD laugh]
(Chandong) Then...
I'll discuss it with
our US co-production partner
and get back to you.
There probably won't be any major issues.
(Lee Chan) If you give me
the opportunity, I'll do my best.
(PD) Well, it's going to be shot
entirely on location in LA.
Check this here.
Once you're officially cast,
why don't you come early
to get accustomed to the location?
They've already booked a villa there.
(Chandong) You can get some rest there
like you're on vacation,
and join us for meetings or table reads.
[exhales]
(Wonbin) I think it's a great idea.
You could get adjusted
to the time difference.
Yes, that sounds great.
[Chandong laughs]
[PD reacts]
[Wonbin sighs]
[Wonbin exclaims]
(Wonbin) Chan. At this point,
you've got the role
[button clicks]
Congratulations.
[clasping hands]
[Wonbin laughs]
You've always wanted to go to Hollywood.
Your dream's finally coming true.
(Lee Chan) It's all thanks to you.
[Wonbin laughs]
(Wonbin) We should sort out
your schedule in Korea first.
[rustles]
(Lee Chan) Will I be in the States
for a long time?
Well, yeah. It'll be shot entirely in LA.
(Wonbin) But this could really
make your career.
(Dareum
Yes, I got home safely! Get some rest!)
[rustles]
[Wonbin sighs]
Are you dating, by any chance?
[Lee Chan scoffs]
Chan.
You've had paparazzi on your tail
these past few days,
and this is a crucial time for you.
[elevator dings]
[elevator doors opening]
[taps]
[button clicks]
I know that too...
[announcement plays]
[Dareum gasps]
[Dareum, Hagi gasp]
[intriguing music]
Mr. Kang.
[laughs]
[Hagi reacts]
[clears throat]
Ms. Nam.
[Dareum reacts]
You must be here to buy stuff for Koong.
(Hagi) Yes.
Does Jjak like this too?
(Dareum) Yes, totally.
The moment I hold this,
Jjak suddenly turns into a predator.
[Hagi scoffs]
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
Then I should get one of each.
[Dareum reacts]
[music stops]
[thuds]
I see you're not working late today.
(Hagi) I usually work at home these days.
I feel like Koong waits for me all day.
I do too...
[laughs awkwardly]
(Hagi) Then should we meet up sometime?
[reacts]
[ding sound]
(Dareum) What?
[dramatic sound]
[intriguing music]
(Hagi) Oh...
I mean...
Well...
I meant Koong and Jjak.
We should let them play together.
[Dareum reacts]
Right.
He startled me.
[thud sound]
[bright music]
[exciting sound]
[thuds]
Gosh.
So I wasn't the only one who was affected.
[phone vibrating]
[music stops]
(Chan)
(Dareum) Let me take this.
(Hagi) Sure.
[vibration continues]
[phone clacks]
Hi.
[intriguing music]
[thud sound]
[flinching sound]
(Dareum) I was going to call you
when I got home...
[music stops]
[laughs awkwardly]
No...
I'm fine.
[calm music]
Yes, I got home safely last night.
What happened to that urgent business?
(Lee Chan) It went well.
Thanks for asking.
That's a relief.
(Lee Chan) Dareum, there's something
I really want to say to you.
Do you have time tomorrow evening?
I'll send you the address.
Let's meet after work.
[exhales]
Okay.
(Lee Chan) And...
Can I call you back later?
- (Lee Chan) Sure. Okay.
- (Dareum) Bye.
[call ending sound]
Sorry about that.
(Hagi) It's fine.
[music stops]
(Hagi) Was that...
the man...
from the blind date?
(Dareum) What?
[laughs awkwardly]
Yes.
(Hagi) He contacted you again
after leaving like that?
(Dareum) Oh...
I guess he felt bad.
[sighs]
He shouldn't have left you like that
if he was going to feel bad.
It's not like he's some celebrity
or something.
[flinching sound]
(Hagi) How busy could he possibly be?
[laughs awkwardly]
Right...
(Hagi) Ms. Nam, do you know
that you said you were fine just now too?
[sighs]
Did I...
[laughs awkwardly]
say that again?
(Hagi) No matter
what kind of person he is,
there's no reason for you
to bend over backwards for him.
[soft music]
[faint laugh]
You're right.
(Dareum) To tell you the truth,
it wasn't a blind date.
He's someone I've liked from afar
for a long time.
But...
once I started seeing him...
[sighs]
I found myself trying to accommodate him
when he didn't even ask me to.
I always
prioritized him before myself,
and my feelings came second.
[deep sigh]
So I actually...
feel a bit confused.
(Hagi) Then just set one rule.
Think about...
whether he makes you more like yourself,
or...
makes you feel smaller.
Whatever you decide,
just think about whether it's a choice
true to you.
[music stops]
[beeps]
- (automated voice) Payment completed.
- (employee) Here you go.
[grabs bottle]
[street noise]
[lid clicks]
(Dareum) It wasn't a blind date.
[whoosh sound]
He's someone
I've liked from afar for a long time.
[whoosh sound]
[spits]
[somber music]
[coughs]
[comical sound]
He's someone
[deep sigh]
I've liked from afar for a long time.
[bubble popping sound]
Liked from afar...
for a long time...
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me...
[laughs]
(Dareum) I'll give it a try.
[sparkling sound]
[music stops]
I'll be more like myself.
I really like you.
[voice echoing] I really like you.
[passionate music]
[laughs]
[sparkling sound]
(Hagi) This is so annoying.
Darn it...
[music stops]
Who the hell is he?
[tapping keyboard]
(Welcome, Hagi
What can I help you with today?)
[scoffs]
[intriguing music]
[tapping keyboard]
(Disappointed after meeting
someone you've liked)
[beep sound]
- (Luni) Hello!
- Oh, my gosh!
[music stops]
(Luni) Would you like me to share
some helpful information
about your search?
[comical sound]
[sighs]
[whoosh sound]
[cheerful music]
(Hagi) Well...
Go on, then.
(Luni) It's common to feel disappointed
when you finally meet someone
you've idealized for a long time.
It's a feeling that comes from the gap
between expectations and reality.
[whoosh sound]
Right?
You should date someone who likes you
instead of clinging to a crush.
Don't you think?
(Luni) Statistically,
stable romantic relationships
[swish sound]
are more likely to develop
with someone close
who expresses their interest first
instead of someone
you've had a one-sided crush on
for a long time.
"Someone close"?
[sparkling sound]
(Luni) Someone close.
[music stops]
[street sounds]
[paper rustling]
You did a great job.
(Hagi) Let's proceed with this.
[laughs]
(Dareum) Okay. I'll do my best
with the preparations.
Ms. Nam.
(Dareum) Yes?
What are you doing this evening?
(Dareum) Excuse me?
(Hagi) Oh...
[cheerful music]
I mean...
Let's meet...
with Koong and Jjak.
Right!
But I actually have plans today.
[reacts]
Then let me know when you're free.
Yes, Mr. Kang.
[door closes]
Plans?
[intriguing music]
[thud sound]
(Hagi) She has plans?
Could she be meeting that guy?
[comical sound]
(Dareum) Can I call you back later?
[bubble popping sound]
[Hagi laughs]
[tapping sound]
No way.
It can't be.
[music stops]
[door opens]
(employee) Hello. Come inside, ma'am.
[elegant music plays]
(Dareum) Okay.
[door closes]
[rattling]
Sir.
[Dareum laughs]
- You're here.
- (Dareum) Yes.
(employee) Let me know
if you need anything.
(Dareum) Thank you.
But why are we...
[inhales]
I have something to celebrate.
(Lee Chan) So I wanted to do
some shopping quietly
and enjoy a date with you.
[Lee Chan, Dareum laugh]
Right!
Do you want to try this on?
This?
I think it'll suit you.
[Dareum laughs]
(Dareum) It's pretty.
[faint laugh]
[laughs awkwardly]
[Dareum grunts]
(Dareum) Do I look okay?
Yeah. You look great.
[Dareum reacts]
(employee) Neutral tones really suit you.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
(Lee Chan) It looks great on you.
Try this on too.
I really don't think this will suit me.
It'll look different once you try it on.
[grunts]
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
[uplifting music]
[grunts]
[laughs awkwardly]
[faint laugh]
[door closes]
[exclaims]
(Dareum) I look weird, don't I?
(Lee Chan) Not at all.
You look so pretty.
[exhales]
I don't usually...
wear clothes like this.
That's why I like it even more.
(Lee Chan) I'm surprised
at how this look suits you too.
[laughs awkwardly]
Dareum, just a moment.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
[Lee Chan laughs]
(Lee Chan) You could wear this
when we go to LA.
(Dareum) LA?
(Lee Chan) Yes.
[music fades]
(Dareum) Then it's almost confirmed.
Wow. You're working
with Director Park Chandong.
[elegant music plays]
That's so cool.
[laughs]
(Lee Chan) They're still
finalizing everything.
Still, I wanted you to be
the first one to know.
It's all thanks to your support.
Thank you, Dareum.
[Dareum reacts]
I'm so happy for you, Chan.
[Dareum laughs]
[Dareum reacts]
[glasses clink]
[exhales]
But...
are you filming in the States?
(Lee Chan) Yeah.
[Lee Chan inhales]
We'll start filming in LA
early next year.
[Dareum reacts]
(Lee Chan) But the schedule
isn't confirmed yet.
Then...
I won't be able to see you for a while.
Why don't you come with me?
(Dareum) What?
(Lee Chan) They're going to prepare
a car and housing in LA.
[calm music]
While I'm filming,
you can study fashion there.
Then we can keep seeing each other.
[Dareum grunts]
What about work?
We can work that out.
Lots of people work remotely these days.
(Lee Chan) Gaining experience there
might be better for you.
[Dareum reacts]
I'm sure you'll love it there.
There are a lot of shows there,
and lots of brands.
[laughs awkwardly]
I guess...
that's true.
(Lee Chan) That's why
I picked one out for you too.
[Dareum grunts]
I have something to give you too.
(Lee Chan) What is it?
[rustles]
[Dareum grunts]
[rattles]
(Lee Chan) A cardholder.
(Dareum) Yes. I made it myself
at a leather workshop.
(Lee Chan) You did a good job.
It'll be too precious to use.
[laughs awkwardly]
Thank you.
[sighs]
[music stops]
LA...
[calm music]
(Hagi) Whatever you decide,
[whoosh sound]
just think about whether it's a choice
true to you.
[whoosh sound]
[sighs]
(APPELLO
Outstanding employee)
[faint sigh]
(Proposal for APPELLO Brand Expansion
Marketing Team Nam Dareum)
(APPELLO
Nam Dareum)
[rattles]
[Dareum sighs]
[pen clicks]
[writing sound]
[music fades]
[insects chirping]
(Mimi) Exhale as you go up.
[Minwoo grunts]
[majestic music]
And inhale as you go down.
[exhales]
[inhales]
Come up a little bit more.
[Minwoo grunts]
[Minwoo groans]
[comical sound]
And pause here. One, two.
[Minwoo grunts]
[Minwoo exclaims]
[creaking sound]
All right!
[Minwoo exhales]
That's it for today.
[Minwoo sighs]
[rustles]
Please clean up your space.
(Minwoo) Okay.
[grunts]
[Minwoo exhales]
[music fades]
- (Mimi) Good work today.
- (Minwoo) Thank you.
[Minwoo grunts and pants]
I...
[Minwoo grunts]
[cheerful music]
(Mimi) Minwoo!
[whoosh sound]
You'll attend
the last session next time, right?
[bubble popping sounds]
[grunts]
I'm sure she was giving me a sign.
[music stops]
Was I mistaken?
[wiping]
[door closes]
(Minwoo) I...
Thank you for today.
You too.
(Minwoo) Right.
[bright music]
I'll get going now, then.
Bye!
- (Mimi) Minwoo.
- (Minwoo) Yes?
[whoosh sound]
Aren't we going together?
Right?
(Minwoo) We're having
a meal together, right?
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
[Minwoo laughs]
[music stops]
(Minwoo) This looks delicious.
[upbeat music plays]
You must be hungry.
(Mimi) Thank you.
[clatters]
It was pretty tough today, right?
(Minwoo) No, not at all.
I can handle that much.
Thank you.
(Mimi) You must be pretty outgoing,
hitting on people at places like this.
[ding sound]
(Minwoo) How did you get here?
[whoosh sound]
(Mimi) By bus.
[cheerful music]
(Minwoo) Then you can
go on a date with me on the way back.
[shattering sound]
(Minwoo) Oh, you remember that?
[groans]
It was my first time!
I mean it.
I'm actually an introvert,
and I've never dated before.
That day...
I fell for you at first sight
and mustered up my courage.
[faint laugh]
That's what you say to every girl, right?
(Minwoo) Yes.
I'm just kidding.
I usually...
[music stops]
get a bit talkative
when I'm with someone I like.
Why?
Because I'm trying to pretend
that I'm not nervous.
Then...
what about now?
I'm in this state right now.
[trembling sound]
[whoosh sound]
[comical sound]
[laughs]
[bright music]
That was funny, right? It worked.
[Mimi clears throat]
(Mimi) Anyway,
thank you for dealing
with that customer last time.
(Minwoo) Don't mention it.
But...
(Mimi) how do you know
all the terms and conditions?
Nobody reads that.
It's a habit.
(Minwoo) A habit of thinking about winning
whenever I get in an argument.
A habit?
(Minwoo) Well...
[laughs awkwardly]
Reading is part of my job.
[faint laugh]
[glasses clink]
(Mimi) Who is this guy?
There's an unexpected charm to him.
[faint laugh]
[glass clunks]
[music stops]
[elegant music plays]
[Lee Chan laughs]
(Lee Chan) You gave it an update.
Wow, there's an LA version now.
[rustling]
(Dareum) You've always said
that going to Hollywood was your dream.
(Lee Chan) Yeah.
So I've imagined it loads of times too.
(Lee Chan) Then...
we can do all of these together.
[laughs]
Seeing the stars at the observatory,
walking on the beach together...
It's a perfect date plan.
[laughs]
(Dareum) Chan.
I have something to tell you.
Something to tell me?
[inhales]
(Dareum) I...
liked spending time
with you.
I felt excited too.
But...
I couldn't...
be honest.
What do you mean?
I couldn't be honest with you
or...
with myself.
(Dareum) So today,
I'll stop pretending to be okay
and be honest with you.
[inhales]
[laughs]
[grunts]
I thought that
when I was with someone I liked,
I'd be able
to laugh,
cry, whine, express anger,
and share all my emotions with them.
But...
I...
couldn't really
do that with you.
[calm music]
I think
I still consider you
as someone
I admire
rather than a romantic partner.
Of course, I still support your dream,
but I have my own dream too now.
Going to the States would be great,
but I love APPELLO,
and I love the work
I'm doing here more.
So...
I want to remain an employee of APPELLO
and as...
your fan.
[Dareum exhales]
[music stops]
[street sounds]
[Yeongwoo scoffs]
Nam Dareum mode has started again.
"Nam Dareum mode"? What's that?
(Yeongwoo) Remember last time
when we made the challenge video?
She worked even harder when
we were told to stop working on it.
[Mina reacts]
Nam Dareum mode turns on
when she's at the edge of a cliff!
Ms. Nam, you're not standing
at the edge of a cliff, are you?
Is something going on?
No, it's nothing...
I just like that I can take
my mind off things.
[laughs awkwardly]
[rattling]
(Mina) Ms. Nam,
what happened to your hand?
Did you hurt yourself?
(Dareum) Oh, this?
I'm fostering a kitten right now.
[Mina, Yeongwoo gasps]
I need to find a home for the kitten,
but I've been too busy these days.
(Yeongwoo) A kitten?
I was actually preparing to adopt one.
Hang on... Can I see a photo?
- Really?
- (Yeongwoo) Yeah!
Hang on.
Mr. Park, you like animals?
Yes, I love them.
Me too.
[Dareum inhales]
(Dareum) Isn't it cute?
[cat meowing sound]
[cheerful music]
[Mina, Yeongwoo gasp]
Its name is Jjak.
I actually found two of them together.
They're Koong and Jjak.
Oh, gosh. It's so cute!
I swear, I really wanted
to adopt an orange cat.
- For real?
- (Yeongwoo) For real.
Here's another photo.
[Yeongwoo, Mina gasp]
(Mina) It's so cute!
[Yeongwoo reacts]
(Mina) So cute.
[music stops]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[Wonbin exhales]
(Wonbin) Director Park Chandong's script.
Chan!
You've officially been cast!
[claps]
Yeah!
[Wonbin exclaims]
Wow...
What is it? Is it hard to believe?
(Lee Chan) What?
No, I'm just really happy.
[scoffs]
Is that the problem?
(Wonbin) All right.
Let's save the celebration for later.
There's a lot to prepare for
since it's shot in the States.
We have to adjust your schedule,
get a visa, get in shape...
And if there's anything you need,
write up a list...
I don't think I can just leave like this.
[taps]
(Wonbin) Chan! Where are you going?
[door closes]
[knocks]
[Dareum reacts]
Mr. Kang.
You haven't gone home yet?
(Dareum) Oh...
[laughs awkwardly]
I want to get some more done
before I leave.
[thuds]
[bright music]
It's fine...
[Hagi sighs]
Thank you.
(Hagi) Do you
not have a date today?
(Dareum) No.
[inhales]
There's so much work,
I don't have time for a date.
Why are you doing everything on your own?
(Hagi) I didn't tell you to do that.
[laughs awkwardly]
My colleagues helped me out earlier.
(Dareum) But...
I just wanted to finish up by myself.
It must be tough suddenly being in charge
of a large event.
[inhales]
[laughs awkwardly]
I do feel a bit overwhelmed,
but still...
(Dareum) I feel proud
being in charge of a project.
(Hagi) I'm sure you'll learn
a lot of things
during the process.
(Dareum) Right.
[gasps]
Right.
Mr. Park said he wants
to adopt Koong and Jjak.
What?
You're sending them away already?
I do feel sad about sending them away,
but this is a great opportunity
for Koong and Jjak.
Well, that's true.
(Dareum) Yeah.
[laughs]
I bought a lot of toys for Koong, though.
What else did you buy this time?
(Dareum) I told you
that you didn't need to buy more.
[claps]
Where did you buy them?
(Hagi) Just somewhere...
[music stops]
[Dareum laughs]
[elevator doors opening]
(Miyeong) Ms. Nam?
She said she'll be working late today.
[elevator doors closing]
[card reader beeps]
[door closes]
[sad music]
[music stops]
[faint laugh]
Mr. Kang.
(Dareum) Do you remember
what you told me last time?
(Hagi) What do you mean?
[rustles]
You told me to think about whether
the choice I make is true to myself.
[Hagi laughs]
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
(Dareum) Thanks to what you said...
I mustered up my courage.
[calm music]
[grunts]
For the first time,
I was really honest.
And I made a choice true to myself.
[laughs]
Thank you, Mr. Kang.
You were just always someone
who could make
that choice.
[laughs awkwardly]
Hearing you say it like that,
I guess it's true.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
(Hagi) So she ended things...
[rattles]
with that man.
Ms. Nam.
(Dareum) Yes?
I have something to say...
[door opens]
(Lee Chan) You're working late.
[music stops]
[door closes]
(Hagi) What brings you here?
(Lee Chan) I heard you were working late
because of the pop-up event.
So these are the DIY kits?
Yes, Director.
[quiet music]
How do I do this?
(Lee Chan) Teach me.
(Hagi) Sit down.
[chair rattles]
[playful music]
You're really fast, Director.
(Lee Chan) I've signed over
a thousand albums in one day, you know.
This is nothing.
Fold them properly.
Don't just rush through them.
Pay attention to the details.
[laughs]
Yes, Mr. Kang.
Ms. Nam, here.
(Dareum) Oh...
[thuds]
[music stops]
(Lee Chan) But Ms. Nam,
who are you more compatible with?
Him or me?
[intriguing music]
(Dareum) Excuse me?
Why are you asking that?
You know, people have preferences.
[Dareum grunts]
[Dareum stammers]
I...
[laughs awkwardly]
Well...
[Dareum stammers]
I...
[laughs awkwardly]
I'm still a new employee...
And you have
different personalities, so...
That's a safe, diplomatic answer.
[music stops]
(Lee Chan) I was just...
wondering if you're more drawn
to one of us.
[calm music]
[faint sigh]
[rattling]
[music stops]
[thuds]
[grabs]
[somber music]
Let me talk to you.
[music fades]
(Hagi) Did you...
really come here because of work?
(Lee Chan) Why?
(Hagi) And when you came
to Ms. Im Cheongrim's home too.
This is an important project.
Do you...
like Ms. Nam, by any chance?
[ominous music]
[exhales]
I do.
She's my favorite employee.
(Lee Chan) Who wouldn't like her
when she works so hard?
Only as an employee?
What is it you want to hear?
You were going
to go after Ms. Nam just now too.
What about you?
(Lee Chan) Are you protecting an employee,
or are you threatened by me?
You're not telling me either.
If you're honest with me,
[Lee Chan sighs]
then I'll be honest too.
[music fades]
[sighs]
(Lee Chan) Ms. Nam,
who are you more compatible with?
Him or me?
[calm music]
I want
[birds singing]
to date you, Dareum.
I'm sorry about that day.
(Dareum) It's fine.
(Lee Chan) I feel bad
just letting you go like this.
(Dareum) I'm really fine.
[Dareum laughs]
(Hagi) You're not fine.
At least to me,
you can say that you're not fine.
[writing]
[faint sigh]
(Lee Chan) I was just
wondering if you're more drawn
to one of us.
[inhales]
[music stops]
[doorbell rings]
[insects chirping]
(Seula) Just a moment!
[door lock sound]
Thank you.
[rustles]
(delivery man) Enjoy your food,
and have a great day.
[thud sound]
[uplifting music]
(Roy) Have a great day.
[whoosh sound]
I hope my voice brings happiness
to your everyday life.
This was Roy of D.N.X.
[thuds]
[music stops]
[engine revs]
[Seula pants]
I'm sure that was Roy's voice.
[pants]
[door opens]
[ominous music]
(Yeongwoo) No...
[Mina grunts]
[music stops]
(Yeongwoo) I wanted
to have kalguksu today.
[Mina groans]
(Dareum) We failed again.
When will we ever
get to try the kalguksu?
I don't think we'll have a chance
unless we take the morning off
and wait in line for hours.
I really wanted to try that place.
[Mina grunts]
(Mina) Me too.
Why don't we go up to the rooftop garden
and walk off our meal?
- (Yeongwoo) Sounds great.
- (Mina) Right?
I have work to do,
so I'll head inside first.
[Dareum laughs]
Then should we go together?
[Dareum reacts]
(Mina) Sure!
- (Dareum) See you later.
- (Yeongwoo) Okay.
[button clicks]
(Mina) See you later.
[card reader beeps]
[Dareum reacts]
[Hyesu grunts]
Ms. Seo, didn't you have lunch?
(Hyesu) I should eat now.
I guess you had lunch early.
- Yes. Enjoy your lunch.
- (Hyesu) Yeah.
[Dareum laughs]
[door opens]
[ominous sound effect]
[tense music]
Did Ms. Cheon clean here?
[ominous sound effect]
[music fades]
[Minwoo scoffs]
People would think
you're moving away at this hour.
Why do you have so much stuff
for just one cat?
[bell ringing]
They just piled up.
(Minwoo) Here.
[door closes]
[cat meowing]
Hand the cat over safely,
and tell her how you feel too.
[bubble popping sound]
[cheerful music]
What are you talking about?
(Minwoo) Today's the perfect opportunity.
Don't miss it.
[cat meowing]
Make sure to tell her!
(Hagi) Jeez. Just go.
[Hagi grunts]
Good luck, okay?
- (Hagi) Go.
- (Minwoo) I'm going.
Tell her how I feel?
[comical sound]
(Minwoo) Tell her how you feel too.
[bubble popping sound]
[inhales]
[comical sound]
(Luni) Someone close.
[bubble popping sound]
[sighs]
[music stops]
[clicks]
[cat meowing]
[phone vibrating]
[bells ringing]
(Dareum) Hang on.
[message notification sound]
(Hagi) Let's meet around eight.
[Dareum reacts]
[message notification sound]
(Dareum) Okay. Koong and Jjak
are finally meeting.
(Hagi) There's a lot of luggage,
so I'll head over to your place.
[message notification sound]
I'm heading out now.
He really is considerate.
[phone clacks]
[thuds]
[gasps]
[dramatic music]
[whoosh sound]
[gasps]
[sparkling sound]
(Lee Chan) See you, Dareum!
[gasps]
[thud sound]
[whoosh sound]
[gasps]
If Mr. Kang sees this...
[music stops]
No!
[exciting music]
[thud sound]
[Dareum yelps]
Darn it...
[grunts]
[Dareum grunts]
[clatters]
All right...
[pants]
[whoosh sound]
[music stops]
[groans]
[brushes hands]
[thuds]
[sighs]
[comical sound]
(Minwoo) Tell her how you feel too.
[bubble popping sound]
[Dareum gasps]
(Dareum) Hi, Koong.
[cat meowing]
[exclaims]
[Hagi brushes hands]
Hang on.
[cat meowing]
It must have been heavy.
Thank you, Mr. Kang.
(Hagi) It's nothing.
(Dareum) Right!
Wear these.
Well, I...
(Dareum) Yes?
It's my first time at a woman's place...
[cheerful music]
(Dareum) I see...
(Hagi) Please excuse me.
[laughs awkwardly]
Right.
Make yourself at home.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
[Dareum laughs]
Take your time.
[music stops]
[boiling]
[bubble popping sound]
[whoosh sound]
[intriguing music]
[cup clinks]
[door closes]
[Hagi clears throat]
[Dareum grunts]
[rattles]
[cup thuds]
[pouring]
Here, have some tea.
Thank you.
[laughs awkwardly]
[cat meowing]
[music fades]
(Dareum) Jjak.
[Dareum grunts]
Koong is here.
Jjak has grown a lot.
Really?
Isn't Koong a similar size?
Well, Koong...
[grunts]
Where did Koong go?
[Dareum grunts]
Koong.
[cat meowing]
[cheerful music]
When did Koong go all the way over there?
I'll get Koong.
[music stops]
- Koong.
- (Dareum) What?
(Hagi) Koong.
[tense music]
[panting]
(Dareum) Hang on, Jjak.
No...
Koong.
[whoosh sound]
- (Dareum) Wait!
- (Hagi) Oh, gosh...
[music stops]
You can't look in here!
My secret...
[intriguing music]
(Dareum) I mean...
My underwear is in there...
(Hagi) Oh...
Sorry. Then...
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
I won't look.
[Dareum sighs]
[whoosh sound]
["peek-a-boo" sound]
[Dareum gasps]
[whoosh sound]
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
If you wait over there,
I'll bring Koong out.
Okay.
[Dareum exhales]
I can't see anything right now.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
Right...
[Dareum grunts]
[music stops]
[relieved sigh]
That was the biggest crisis of my life.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[playful music]
I can't keep hiding the fact
[music stops]
that I'm Chan's fan...
Should I...
just tell him the truth?
[bells ringing]
[Dareum laughs]
[cat meowing]
(Hagi) They do seem
to recognize each other.
(Dareum) Right. Isn't that cool?
You said
they fought and stole each other's food
when they were together.
(Hagi) Fighting when you're together
and missing each other
when you're apart...
I guess it's the same
with people
and cats.
[laughs]
[cat meowing]
(Dareum) This is the perfect time.
(Dareum) Mr. Kang.
To be honest...
(Hagi) Yes?
[stammers]
Well...
[phone vibrating]
I've...
(Hagi) Just a moment.
[taps]
Hello.
I'm out right now,
so I'll check when I get home.
[call ending sound]
What were you saying?
(Dareum) What?
[grunts]
[laughs awkwardly]
I just wanted to thank you
for bringing Koong here.
(Hagi) I should be thanking you.
I got to see Jjak again
thanks to you.
[Dareum laughs]
And it's nice seeing you...
too.
[lively music]
Look at the time.
[Dareum reacts]
I should get going now.
That's so sudden.
[Dareum grunts]
(Hagi) Get some rest, Ms. Nam.
[Dareum reacts]
Bye, Koong.
[cat meowing]
I'll see you at work, then.
Right...
[door lock sound]
(Dareum) Get home safely, Mr. Kang!
(Hagi) Okay.
[door closes]
[door lock sound]
[music stops]
She must've understood, right?
(Hagi) And it's nice seeing you...
[whoosh sound]
too.
Nice seeing you...
too...
[soft music]
Me too.
(Dareum) What?
No...
[Dareum grunts]
[music stops]
[hairdryer whirs]
[elegant music plays]
(Choi) Yes, it's her.
But how did you get photos
from the office?
[laughs]
Really?
That's no surprise.
Then I'll look forward to the article.
[call ending sound]
[taps]
[phone clunks]
[doorbell rings]
(Lee Chan, staff) Hello.
- (Wonbin) Hello.
- (staff) You're here.
- This way, please.
- (Lee Chan) Okay.
- (staff) We'll be ready for you soon.
(Choi) I heard you got cast
in Director Park Chandong's film.
Congratulations, Chan.
Thanks.
(Choi) I'm probably going to start
a global project as well.
I'm filming in the States too.
The States?
Yeah. Isn't that crazy timing?
(Choi) I guess we're meant
to keep running into each other.
[street sounds]
[elevator dings]
[elevator doors opening]
[Dareum, Yeongwoo laugh]
- (Dareum) They're so cute.
- (Yeongwoo) Yeah.
I could hardly sleep the last few days.
[button beeps]
They're so cute.
[thuds]
Oh, my gosh.
[whoosh sound]
[intriguing music]
- (Dareum) Mr. Kang.
- (Yeongwoo) Mr. Kang.
[taps]
[comical sound]
You're getting off work together?
(Dareum) Yes.
Mr. Park's coming to take the cats.
I was on my way out too.
We can go together.
[Dareum reacts]
[whoosh sound]
I'll give you a ride.
[Yeongwoo reacts]
(Hagi) It's on the way.
(Dareum) That's great.
[Dareum laughs]
[faint laugh]
[whoosh sound]
[spinning sound]
[sparkling sound]
[squeaking sound]
[whoosh sound]
[laughing sound]
[music stops]
[cat meowing]
Koong, Jjak, goodbye.
(Dareum) Don't forget me, okay?
[cat meowing continues]
Bye.
[Yeongwoo clears throat]
(Yeongwoo) I'll take good care
of Koong and Jjak.
And Mr. Kang, thank you
for helping with the luggage.
- Right.
- (Dareum) Bye, Mr. Park.
By the way...
[cat meowing]
(Dareum) Yes?
It's nothing.
[Yeongwoo laughs]
[cheerful music]
I...
[Yeongwoo sighs]
[whoosh sound]
[Dareum laughs]
[drumroll sound]
[bell ringing sound]
[whoosh sound]
If you're not in a hurry to leave,
why don't we hang out a bit
as colleagues...
I mean, with Mr. Kang as well...
[claps]
How about some coffee?
[Dareum reacts]
(Hagi) Not today.
Cats can get really stressed
in an unfamiliar environment.
They should be with their guardian
on their first day.
[Dareum reacts]
(Yeongwoo) Oh, right.
Then I guess
we'll have to take a rain check.
Next time, then.
[Yeongwoo laughs]
(Hagi) You should hurry home
and help them settle down.
[music stops]
All right. I'll get going now!
(Dareum) Bye.
(Yeongwoo) Ms. Nam,
let's hang out together soon.
[Dareum laughs]
Without Mr. Kang.
[laughs]
Sure.
[door closes]
[car engine revs]
(Dareum) Take care, Koong, Jjak.
Take care of each other.
[Dareum sighs]
(Hagi) And don't fight.
[sniffles]
[lively music]
[Dareum grunts]
[Dareum sniffles and clears throat]
Ms. Nam, are you crying?
[Dareum grunts]
(Dareum) No.
I guess I've grown attached to them.
To be honest,
I feel like I've grown more attached.
I liked how you asked
if Koong ate well every day,
and I found myself looking forward
to your random photos.
Right.
Without them...
[laughs awkwardly]
there won't be a reason
to message you anymore.
(Hagi) I...
[stomach grumbling sound echoes]
[music fades]
[comical sound]
[Dareum exclaims]
[cheerful music]
[Dareum laughs]
What's wrong with my stomach?
[stomach grumbling]
Should we have dinner?
It'd be a shame to just go home.
[exclaims]
Sure. Sounds good.
(Hagi) Okay.
[Dareum laughs]
- Let's go.
- (Dareum) Okay.
[music stops]
(employee) Next party, please.
(Dareum) I really wanted to come here.
How did you know about this place?
(Hagi) Well...
(Kalguksu)
I heard this place was popular.
Yeah. It is.
[intriguing music]
(Dareum) We failed again.
[Mina groans]
When will we ever
get to try the kalguksu?
[Dareum sighs]
I really wanted to try that place.
- (Mina) Me too.
- Kalguksu?
[blip sound]
Kalguksu place nearby...
[typing sound]
[blip sound]
[beep sound]
(Kalguksu)
Found it.
[whoosh sound]
[customers murmuring]
You wanted to eat this that badly?
(Dareum) Yes!
It's really hard to eat here
since you can't make a reservation.
(customer 1) Over here!
[rustles]
[thuds]
(customer 2) Sorry.
[faint laugh]
Stand on this side, Ms. Nam.
(Dareum) Thank you.
[music stops]
[laughs awkwardly]
(employee) Two bowls of kalguksu.
- (Dareum) Thank you.
- (employee) Enjoy.
(Dareum) The soup looks so delicious.
I can already tell it'll be amazing.
[Hagi grunts]
What is it?
Is it not to your taste?
[slurps]
This is really tasty.
Right? I told you it'll be amazing!
[soft music]
[laughs]
Let's eat.
[slurps]
[Dareum exclaims]
[Dareum exclaims and claps]
(Dareum) It's really good.
[Hagi laughs]
(Dareum) That was so good.
It's really worth the wait, isn't it?
(Hagi) Yeah.
[music fades]
Mr. Kang, look.
(Dareum) Doesn't that look
exactly like Jjak?
[cat meowing sound]
That expression
and that tightly closed mouth.
It looks just like Jjak.
[laughs]
How cute!
- Should I get it for you?
- (Dareum) What?
Mr. Kang!
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[rattling]
[exclaims]
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[sighs]
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[sighs]
I got it! I...
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[Dareum sighs]
[sighs]
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[Hagi grunts]
[music stops]
[sighs]
Mr. Kang,
(Dareum) I think you've done enough.
I already had plenty of fun watching.
(Hagi) No.
I can see the pattern now.
(Dareum) What?
(Hagi) The claw's grip strength
is consistent,
but if you look closely,
it's slightly tilted to the left.
Just now,
[taps]
I got it from the wrong angle.
What...
Why are you so serious about winning that?
Well, I have a goal.
(Hagi) I have to get Jjak.
[cheerful music]
This will be my final try.
[coin rattles]
[claw machine beeps]
[scoffs]
[claw whirs]
(Hagi) Okay...
[Hagi grunts]
[claw machine stops]
[Hagi sighs]
[music stops]
[Dareum laughs]
[sighs]
(Dareum) Calculating the angle,
coming up with a strategy...
You were like a total pro.
(Hagi) I wanted to get you
the plushie that looked like Jjak.
- Sorry.
- (Dareum) Not at all!
This guy is cute too.
[laughs]
And so were you.
[lively music]
[baby laughing sound]
(Hagi) I...
had fun today.
[faint laugh]
Me too.
And...
even without Koong and Jjak,
(Hagi) you can still message me
without a particular reason.
I...
liked hearing from you
too.
[laughs awkwardly]
(Hagi) You know...
Not as the CEO,
but as just Kang Hagi...
I like...
[phone vibrating]
[music stops]
[phone continues vibrating]
[rustles]
Hang on.
[grunts]
[phone vibrating]
- Hey, Seula.
- (Seula) Hey!
This is crazy!
There's an article
about you and Chan dating!
[somber music]
There's even a photo of you on a date!
(Dareum) What?
(The two were seen on a late-night date,
chatting without a care for onlookers)
[whoosh sound]
Mr. Kang...
Is this...
[music stops]
true?
[calm music]
[sighs]
(Epilogue)
[writing sound]
[music stops]
(Lee Chan) Ms. Nam,
who are you more compatible with?
Him or me?
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
[inhales]
I was just wondering...
if you're more drawn to one of us.
[writing sound]
(Koong, Jjak)
[ding sound]
(Hagi, Dareum)
[writing sound]
[sparkling sound]
[music: "My Bias, My Boss"
theme song continues]
(Hagi) You went on a date,
but you're not dating?
(vlogger) That's not a fan.
That's a total stalker right there.
- (fan) We're boycotting APPELLO!
- (fans) We're boycotting APPELLO!
(Wonbin) The CEO is away right now.
(Lee Chan) Dareum just got branded
as a stalker because of me.
(Dareum) There's nothing going on
between us,
despite what people think.
(Lee Chan) When I asked you
how you felt about Dareum,
did you answer me honestly?
(Hagi) Meet the reporter and settle this.
(Choi) You're doing this
just to protect one girl?
(Dareum) I won't resent you
if you fire me.
(Seula) Stop filming her!
(Minwoo) Do you really
have to go this far?
(Hagi) From now on...
I don't want to cause
further trouble for APPELLO.